hylete.com 2013-12-31

# HYLETE - Privacy Policy

Your privacy is important to us. HYLETE, LLC maintains high standards for the protection of your privacy at our web sites. Here is what you can expect when you visit our site. First, by using, accessing, or viewing this website, you irrevocably agree to the terms and conditions of use placed on this website by HYLETE, LLC, including but not limited to this privacy policy. Our privacy policy may be changed or modified at any time, so it is your responsibility to review this policy each time you visit our website. 

Other than to fulfill a request from you, we won't sell, rent or share any personally-identifiable information you provide without your consent. 

Please remember that this policy covers only the data collection and use practices for our site, an official website of HYLETE, LLC. HYLETE, LLC privacy policies may differ at other of its websites or in its off-line data collection and reporting practices. Questions regarding the privacy policy of any other website should be directed to the privacy policy posted on such other website. Further, HYLETE, LLC is not responsible for the privacy policies of third parties, and upon leaving the official HYLETE, LLC website, you understand that HYLETE, LLC privacy policy no longer applies to the third party website or materials you are viewing or accessing.

**Email**  
If you sign up for any online services, offers or programs, or purchase products from us online, we will use the information you provide to fulfill such order or provide you with such services or programs. If you are sent any email by us and no longer wish to receive any online services, offers or programs, you can always opt-out of future receipt of such communications by following the instructions for opting out on each email received. Your personal information concerning any product purchased may be maintained internally at HYLETE, LLC in order to allow HYLETE, LLC to fulfill warranty obligations and the like. 

**The Information We Collect**  
Our web servers automatically capture your domain name, the IP address of the web page from which you enter our site, the pages you visit on our site and the amount of time you spend here. We do not collect any information that can reveal your personal identity unless you voluntarily provide it when you register to use interactive features of the site, including the sales portal, or to receive information from us or our affiliated companies. If you register a HYLETE, LLC product, enter to win a contest, subscribe to one of our newsletters, or send an email to us, or otherwise transmit information via any of the HYLETE, LLC websites, HYLETE, LLC may obtain and collect personally identifiable contact information (expressed herein generally as "personal information") such as your name, email address, payment information (i.e. credit card number/expiration date), and/or mailing address, subject to your ability to opt-out of our future use or disclosure of such information. Should you wish to opt-out of any website feature or other communications, such as a newsletter you signed up for, then please follow the instructions associated with the website feature opt-out instruction, or the unsubscribe feature of any communication originating with HYLETE, LLC. 

If you have not "opted-out" of our use and disclosure of your personal information, HYLETE, LLC may also use personal information for all marketing and survey purposes on behalf of itself and its affiliates and subsidiaries. HYLETE, LLC may appoint third party agents in connection with such marketing and survey efforts. HYLETE, LLC may disclose personal information to select business partners for use in connection with direct mail marketing efforts, but that personal information will not include your email address. If you have "opted-out", HYLETE, LLC will use or disclose your personal information only as stated above, or: (1) when legally ordered to do so by a lawful subpoena or court order, (2) if you violate or breach an agreement with HYLETE, LLC, (3) if we believe you will harm the property or rights of HYLETE, LLC or those of HYLETE, LLC other customers, (4) under exigent circumstances to protect the physical safety of HYLETE, LLC, its employees, users or the general public, or (5) to validate credit card numbers for charging for fee services you have requested. 

**Chat Rooms and Bulletin Boards**  
HYLETE, LLC may host various chat rooms, bulletin boards, or other means of allowing its customers to publicly communicate with each other. If you participate in any online chat room, bulletin board, or other public means of communication, you acknowledge and agree that your personal information will be publicly available, including your email address. HYLETE, LLC shall have no liability for any use of personal information you make public on its website or in its chat rooms. 

**Children's Privacy**  
Any section of our site that is directed to children or teens will be protected by a screening mechanism to help ensure that parental consent is obtained before we collect or use personal information from children under 13. We do not knowingly collect or use information from children under 13 without the consent of a parent or guardian.

Personally identifiable information voluntarily provided by you may be retained indefinitely for the purposes described in this Privacy Notice. 

**Use of the Information this Site Gathers/Tracks**  
Any personally-identifiable information you give us will be used only to provide the product, service or information you have requested, like retail locations where our products may be found, or to support the programs for which you registered. Unless you specifically consent to let us do so, your personally-identifiable information, including your e-mail address, will not be sold, rented, licensed, or otherwise shared with third parties, other than as required to fulfill a request from you. The non-personally identifiable information we gather in aggregate form may be used to improve our site, and we may share that information with our licensors/licensees, affiliated companies or sponsors.

**Making Changes to the Information You Provide to Us**  
Information that you voluntarily provided will be maintained as long as HYLETE, LLC deems appropriate to fulfill the purpose for which you provided the information or until you request us to remove it.

**Cookies**  
When you visit our site, we may place a temporary "session" or a permanent cookie on your computer that will allow us to customize and enhance your experience at the site, make improvements to our site, or to report site activity. Our session cookies are not permanently stored on your computer and expire when you leave. Permanent cookies are issued only to site visitors who link the site from a search engine and are used only to permit HYLETE, LLC to attract qualified users to the site. Our cookies will never be used to track your activity on any third party web sites or to send spam, nor will they provide us with any personally identifiable information about you. We store cookie information only in aggregate form and use the aggregate information only to make improvements to the site or in internal reports on site activity. You may use your browser controls to refuse to allow cookies to be placed on your computer. Refusing cookies disables our ability to make your return visits to our site easier or to include information about your visit in our regular monitoring of site traffic.

**Sites We Link To**  
If you choose to use any of the links we provide to our member companies, affiliates, licensors/licensees, and other third party resources, you will be leaving our web site and going to a new web site. Protection of your privacy at those other sites will be governed by the privacy policy at that site. We've taken special care selecting the companies that are officially affiliated with our site to try to ensure that they respect your privacy as we do, but please take the time to read the privacy policies at their sites. HYLETE, LLC is not responsible for the use of your personal information by any third party.

**Contact Information**  
If you have any questions or comments or receive any unwanted e-mail from this site, please contact our customer service department via e-mail at [customerservice@hylete.com](mailto:customerservice@hylete.com) or contact us at the below address: 

**HYLETE, LLC**  
135 S. Sierra Ave, Unit 20  
Solana Beach, California 92075  
Phone: (800) 991-6532
